bitium.com 2019-12-06

# Legal | Bitium | Manage Your Apps and Passwords

* ### 1\. General

Bitium is committed to protecting the privacy of your Personal Information and our practice regarding use of your Personal Information is set forth below in this Privacy Policy. As a condition to use of Bitium Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time. In the event of a material change, we will provide notice via email or a prominent notice on the relevant Bitium website. This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to websites owned and controlled by Bitium that link to this Privacy Policy (“Bitium Websites”). Bitium Websites may contain links and access to other third-party websites. Bitium is not responsible for the information practices or the content of such other websites, and you should review the privacy statements of other websites to understand their information practices. 

* ### 2\. Privacy Frameworks

  1. #### 2.1. EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks

Bitium adheres to the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Bitium Services are certified for both Privacy Shield frameworks under the self-certification of Google LLC, which wholly owns Bitium, Inc.. More information about Google’s certification is available at <https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks>, and you can view Google’s certification on the Privacy Shield website at [www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Bitium remains responsible for any of your personal data that is shared under the Onward Transfer Principle with third parties.

If you have an inquiry regarding our privacy practices in relation to our Privacy Shield certification, we encourage you to contact us at [bitium-dpt@google.com](mailto:bitium-dpt@google.com). Bitium is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC). You may also refer a complaint to your local data protection authority and we will work with them to resolve your concern. In certain circumstances, the Privacy Shield Framework provides the right to invoke binding arbitration to resolve complaints not resolved by other means, as described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield Principles.

* ### 3\. Information Collected by Bitium:

Bitium offers a variety of applications and services collectively referred to as “Bitium Services.” Bitium collects information from individuals who visit the Bitium Websites. 

  1. #### 3.1. Personal Information

We collect and store any information you enter when asking for more information about Bitium Services, registering for and using Bitium Services, or provide to us in any other way. For example, when registering for a user account, we request your name and email address, among other information. You will also be asked to choose a unique username and a password, which will be used solely for the purpose of providing access to your user account. Your name and email address will be used to inform you of new services, releases, upcoming events, and material changes to this Privacy Policy.

Bitium will have access to third party personal information provided by you as part of using Bitium Services. This information may include third party names, email addresses, passwords, etc., and will be used solely in conjunction with your use of Bitium Services. We do not share any third party personal information with anyone for promotional purposes, nor do we utilize it for any purposes you do not expressly consent to. If you elect to refer other users to the Bitium Websites, we request their email addresses and names to facilitate the request.

Bitium is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequent transfers to a third party acting on its behalf. Bitium complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data transferred or received pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Bitium is subject to the regulatory enforcement power of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Bitium may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In the event that Bitium posts user/customer testimonials on the Bitium Websites, such testimonials may include names or other personal information. We acquire permission from our users before posting these on the Bitium Websites. Bitium is not responsible for Personal Information users elect to include in their testimonials.

  2. #### 3.2. Usage Details

Bitium may record your usage details such as time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used, and the amount of storage used in order to enhance your experience using the Bitium Services, and to help us provide you the best service possible. 

  3. #### 3.3. Contents of your User Account

We store and maintain usernames, passwords and other data stored in your user account at our facilities in the United States. In order to prevent loss of data due to errors or system failures, we also keep backup copies of data including the contents of your user account. Hence your files and data may remain on our servers even after deletion or termination of your user account. The contents of your user account will not be disclosed except as necessary to use the Bitium Services. 

  4. #### 3.4. Financial Information

In the case of services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments. We will not store your financial information except subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments. Your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on either Bitium’s secure servers or the secure servers of our reputed “Payment Gateway Service Provider” who is required to treat your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

  5. #### 3.5. Visitor Details

We use your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system, and other visitor details collected in our log files to analyze the trends, track user behavior and administer and improve Bitium Websites. 

* ### 4\. Cookies

We use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance your experience of the Bitium Services. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. By selecting ‘keep me signed-in’ or related options in Bitium Services, a permanent cookie will be stored in your computer and you will not be required to sign-in by providing complete login information each time you return to certain parts of our website. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the website. We tie cookie information to your email address when you elect to remain logged in so as to maintain and recall your preferences within the website. We may from time to time employ the use of pixel tags on the website and in emails. Pixel tags such as web beacons are 1x1 images that are embedded onto a web page to document traffic and for website analytics without collecting any Personal Information.

We may from time to time employ the services of a third party agent to analyze statistical and aggregate data about our Bitium Websites content and user base. This aggregated information is not personally identifiable and is employed in improving website functionality and offerings. To this end, these third parties may employ the use of cookies and/or pixel tags in providing their services. While these third party cookies are not tied to your Personal Information, Bitium does not have access to these cookies nor are we responsible for them.

* ### 5\. Links from Bitium Websites

Some pages of Bitium Websites contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of any other websites you access while using the Bitium Services. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide Personal Information, without assuring yourself of the Privacy Policy of other websites. 

* ### 6\. Sharing Information

We may need to disclose Personal Information to our affiliates, service providers and business partners solely for the purpose of providing Bitium Services to you. In such cases Bitium will also ensure that such affiliates, service providers and business partners comply with this Privacy Policy and adopt appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We will obtain your prior specific consent before we share or disclose your Personal Information to any person outside Bitium for any purpose that is not directly connected with providing Bitium Services to you. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Information regarding users with our business partners and advertisers. Please be aware that laws in various jurisdictions in which we operate may obligate us to disclose user information and the contents of your user account to the local law enforcement authorities under a legal process or an enforceable government request. In addition, we may also disclose Personal Information and contents of your user account upon a lawful request by government authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements if disclosure is determined to be necessary by Bitium in our sole and absolute discretion for protecting the safety of our users, employees, or the general public.

Bitium shall remain liable under the Privacy Shield Principles for onward transfers to its agents, if its agent processes Privacy Shield information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Bitium can prove that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

* ### 7\. Legal Requests

Bitium requires appropriate legal process (i.e., subpoena, court order, or other valid process) before disclosing non-public user account information. In the United States, this means Bitium requires a search warrant before disclosing to law enforcement the contents of non-public user communications. Bitium will not provide any non-public user information to non-U.S. law enforcement agencies without a valid U.S. court order (via the mutual legal assistance treaties or letter rogatory). Bitium will attempt to notify users of law enforcement requests for information except where (1) we are legally prohibited from providing notice (e.g. by an order under 18 U.S.C. 2705(b)); (2) an emergency situation exists involving a danger of death or serious physical injury to a person; or (3) we have reason to believe notice wouldn’t go to the actual account holder (e.g. an account has been hijacked). 

* ### 8\. Security

We follow industry appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your user account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees who need to know such information in connection with providing Bitium Services to you and are bound by confidentiality obligations. 

* ### 9\. Information Choices

You will be required to register for our Bitium Services by providing Personal Information. If you choose not to provide your Personal Information, you will not be able to access the Bitium Services. We provide you with the option of opting out from receiving non-transactional mail from us. In the event we decide to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your Personal Information for those other purposes. You may opt out of receiving newsletters and other secondary messages from Bitium by selecting the ‘unsubscribe’ function present in every message we send. 

* ### 10\. Accessing, Updating and Removing Personal Information

We provide users with access to their Personal Information. Users may correct, update or remove any such Personal Information either by accessing their user account or by contacting Bitium Customer Support. Changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect. We respond to all inquiries within 30 days. 

* ### 11\. Legal Requests and Investigation

We may need to provide access to your Personal Information and the contents of your user account to our employees and service providers for the purpose of investigating any suspected illegal activity or potential violation of the terms and conditions for use of Bitium Services. However, Bitium will ensure that such access is in compliance with this Privacy Policy and subject to appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

* ### 12\. Enforcement of Privacy Policy

We make every effort, including periodic reviews to ensure that Personal Information provided by you is used in conformity with this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this Privacy Policy or the manner in which Personal Information is used for the purpose of providing Bitium Services, please contact Bitium Customer Support Services at [support@bitium.com](mailto:support@bitium.com). We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also cooperate with regulatory authorities in this regard if needed.

* ### 13\. Notification of Changes

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on the relevant Bitium Websites in order to keep you informed of any modification in nature of information collected, manner of collection, and use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use Personal Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses unless you have opted out from receiving all email notifications from us. You will not receive email notification of minor changes to the Privacy Policy. If you are concerned about how your Personal Information is used, you should check back <https://www.bitium.com/site/privacy> periodically.

* ### 14\. User-Generated Content

We may provide the capacity for users to post information in public spaces on the Bitium Websites (for example, in our customer support repository). This information may be publicly available to all users and visitors to Bitium. We require registration to publish information, but given the public nature of these spaces, any Personal Information disclosed within these forums may be used to contact users with unsolicited messages. We encourage users to be cautious in disclosure of Personal Information in public forums, as Bitium is not responsible for the Personal Information users elect to disclose.

* ### 15\. Questions

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@bitium.com](mailto:support@bitium.com). We will respond to all inquiries within 30 days of receipt.
